"lang"
{
	"Language" "english"
	"Tokens"
	{
		"FTU_INTRO_001" "Welcome to Apex Legends,"
		"FTU_INTRO_002" "the most dynamic, fast paced, exciting battle royale out there."
		"FTU_INTRO_003" "The battle begins."
		"FTU_INTRO_004" "Now some of you might be asking \"what is an Apex Legends?\""
		"FTU_INTRO_005" "Or even, \"what is a battle royale?\""
		"FTU_INTRO_006" "But don't worry, there are no dumb questions,"
		"FTU_INTRO_007" "This is a safe place."
		"FTU_INTRO_008" "You know and it's probably the only safe place in the game because everywhere else..."
		"FTU_INTRO_009" "someone is trying to kill you."
		"FTU_INTRO_010" "Surprise."
		"FTU_INTRO_011" "Alright, before you go streaking through the sky"
		"FTU_INTRO_012" "assaulting supply ships and tap strafing"
		"FTU_INTRO_013" "your [gibberish] storm point whatever"
		"FTU_INTRO_014" "Hey brah, I'm on my way."
		"FTU_INTRO_015" "Let's cover the basics so you can have the most fun possible as fast as possible."
		"FTU_INTRO_016" "And first up,"
		"FTU_INTRO_017" "the game."
		"FTU_INTRO_018" "The main mode is Battle Royale Trios."
		"FTU_INTRO_019" "It's the game that started it all."
		"FTU_INTRO_020" "Twenty squads of three players drop into a map."
		"FTU_INTRO_021" "The longer you last, the smaller the map gets."
		"FTU_INTRO_022" "Thanks to a shrinking ring."
		"FTU_INTRO_023" "Now the winner is the last squad standing."
		"FTU_INTRO_024" "If we were on the same team, you would be happy about this."
		"FTU_INTRO_025" "You'll start the match on a dropship."
		"FTU_INTRO_026" "You decide when to drop and where to land."
		"FTU_INTRO_027" "But pro tip:"
		"FTU_INTRO_028" "The edges of the map are a bit calmer."
		"FTU_INTRO_029" "Perfect for a new kid on the block such as yourself."
		"FTU_INTRO_030" "No offense,"
		"FTU_INTRO_031" "We all got to start somewhere."
		"FTU_INTRO_032" "Here we go."
		"FTU_INTRO_033" "If you're feeling sassy, you can do"
		"FTU_INTRO_034" "what the cool kids call a hot drop into a popular area."
		"FTU_INTRO_035" "Just don't expect to last long."
		"FTU_INTRO_036" "I need some help over-"
		"FTU_INTRO_037" "Yikes."
		"FTU_INTRO_038" "Dropping on the edges means you can practice your moves"
		"FTU_INTRO_039" "while you explore the map and more importantly, pick up gear, a.k.a."
		"FTU_INTRO_040" "looting."
		"FTU_INTRO_041" "I work hard for the money."
		"FTU_INTRO_042" "This is how you gather the weapons, ammo and equipment"
		"FTU_INTRO_043" "you'll need to survive and fight your way to the final ring."
		"FTU_INTRO_044" "I'll high five you all when I see you."
		"FTU_INTRO_045" "Oh, another pro tip:"
		"FTU_INTRO_046" "You can never have too much loot if you can pick it up,"
		"FTU_INTRO_047" "pick it up."
		"FTU_INTRO_048" "Now, once you feel like you've got the gear"
		"FTU_INTRO_049" "you need to generally kick some ass, then it's time to start shooting."
		"FTU_INTRO_050" "Pew pew pew... that's what guns sound like to me."
		"FTU_INTRO_051" "This game is all about choosing your battles."
		"FTU_INTRO_052" "Just because you can see someone doesn't\nmean you should start shooting at them."
		"FTU_INTRO_053" "Pushing!"
		"FTU_INTRO_054" "Because if they're far away and you've only got a pistol,"
		"FTU_INTRO_055" "popping off at them is just going to get their attention and\nsay,"
		"FTU_INTRO_056" "\"Hey, I don't like living very much and I really don't want to win this game,"
		"FTU_INTRO_057" "so please come kill me, like, right now, please.\""
		"FTU_INTRO_058" "Ambush, ambush!"
		"FTU_INTRO_059" "Yeah, do not do that."
		"FTU_INTRO_060" "Just play smart and always use teamwork."
		"FTU_INTRO_061" "Sheer skill only takes you so far."
		"FTU_INTRO_062" "It's the squads who work together that twerk together-"
		"FTU_INTRO_063" "Or they win, they win because of teamwork and working together."
		"FTU_INTRO_064" "I will save you or die trying."
		"FTU_INTRO_065" "So share your loot,"
		"FTU_INTRO_066" "call out enemies,"
		"FTU_INTRO_067" "Enemy over there."
		"FTU_INTRO_068" "and watch each other's backs."
		"FTU_INTRO_069" "Oh, plus, there's this whole system of nonverbal- uh verbal- uh..."
		"FTU_INTRO_070" "no words, communication for you to use."
		"FTU_INTRO_071" "Some of us kind of need it."
		"FTU_INTRO_072" "Let's defend here."
		"FTU_INTRO_073" "But you'll learn all about that in basic training."
		"FTU_INTRO_074" "Speaking of which, you should probably head there now."
		"FTU_INTRO_075" "Oh, be sure to say hi to my friend Bloodhound."
		"FTU_INTRO_076" "Have you prepared for your end?"
		"FTU_INTRO_077" "I have."
		"FTU_INTRO_078" "They're a total softie."
		"FTU_INTRO_079" "Alright, until next time, I'm Mirage, and it's time to get out of Dodge."
		"FTU_INTRO_080" "No, I'm Mirage and I need a massage."
		"FTU_INTRO_081" "Yeah, that's- no, that's really not working either. But I could use a massage. That sounds good."
	}
}
 