"lang"
{
	"Language" "english"
	"Tokens"		
	{
        "STEAM_EA_ACCOUNT_REQUIRED"							"Apex Legends requires an EA Account to play. Click here to log in or create an account."
        "STEAM_EA_ACCOUNT_ERROR"							"Cannot Access EA Account."
		"STEAM_INGAME_DISABLED"                            	"Steam In-Game-Overlay"
		"STEAM_INGAME_REQUIRED"                            	"Steam in-Game-Overlay is not enabled. Please ensure it is enabled in Steam / Settings / In-Game and restart the game"
        "STEAM_OVERLAY_REQUIRED"                            "This feature requires the Steam Overlay to be enabled. Please enable your Steam Overlay and try again."
        "STEAM_LOGIN_OVERLAY_REQUIRED"						"Linking to your EA Account requires the Steam Overlay to be enabled. Please enable your Steam Overlay and try again."
		"STEAM_IS_OFFLINE"									"Unable to connect to EA Servers. Please check your Internet connection, make sure Steam is online and try again. See ea.com/unable-to-connect for more information."
		"STEAM_UPDATE_AVAILABLE"							"A new Steam Update is available. Please close the game, restart Steam and launch the game again. See ea.com/unable-to-connect for additional information."
        "STEAM_NOT_LOGGED_IN"                              "You need to log in to Steam again to continue. Please open the Steam Client and re-enter your password to log back in. See ea.com/unable-to-connect for additional information."
        "WAITING_FOR_STEAM"									"Waiting for Steam"
		"STEAM_ERROR_OFFLINE"								"Unable to connect to EA Servers. Please check your Internet connection, make sure Steam is online and try again. See ea.com/unable-to-connect for more information."
		"STEAM_ERROR_OVERLAY_INACTIVE"						"The Steam Overlay is inactive. Apex: Legends requires an active Steam Overlay to play."
		"STEAM_REGISTER_BUTTON"								"Register"
	}
}
 